KAREN KELLY

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

SKILLS HTML CSS/SASS Javascript JQuery GitHub UX / UI Photoshop Node Express Angular PostgreSQL

PROFILE

Name

Karen Kelly

Where I Live

Austin, Texas

Call me

512.608.3059

Email me

karenkellydev@gmail.com

See my work

www.karenkellydesign.com

SOCIAL

- @KarenKdesign
- in karenkelly818
- karen818

SUMMARY

A creative problem-solver with excellent communication and leadership skills. Learns new technology quickly and continually strives to increase her programming knowledge while honing her current expertise. She brings a wealth of experience in both client-facing and internal team collaboration. Proficient with a wide array of programming languages and design tools. Unafraid of challenges and embraces change. Excellent potential to become an outstanding team member.

EXPERIENCE

Apr 2016 to

present

Full-Stack Web Developer

Galvanize

- Used the Node, Express, Angular, and PostgreSQL stack to develop both front-end and back-end web applications
- Followed best practices for RESTful CRUD applications, utilizing Agile workflow in a team environment
- · Learned to adapt quickly to new and unfamiliar environments
- Well versed in code review, testing and refactoring techniques as well as writing wellorganized, semantic HTML, CSS/SASS, and Javascript/jQuery code

2013 - 2014 nQueue Billback

Business Development Manager

 Increased new business for Virtual Cabinet, a document management software program, by 50% in the Southwest region

2012 - 2013 LiquidPractice

Director of Sales

- · Signed ten new clients for our beta program in the first month of employment
- Developed and implemented a strategy for bringing clients to the cloud from on-premise server environments.

2010 - 2012 Client Profiles

Regional Sales Manager

- Increased the number of clients in the West Coast, Southwest and Northwest by 30%
- Increased business growth and profitability by establishing and building strategic alliances with clients for sale of legal software technology

2000 - 2010 ProLaw Software / Thomson Reuters

Assistant Sales Manager / Regional Sales Manager

- Promoted to Assistant Sales Manager in less than year due to outstanding job performance
- Earned award for top salesperson in 2001, 2002, 2004, and 2005

EDUCATION

2016 Full-Stack Web Development Fellow

Galvanize

2014 - 2016 Accelerated Programmer Training - Web Development

Austin Community College

1995 - 2000 B.A. - Psychology/Communications

The University of New Mexico -summa cum laude